<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><content type="DNNFAQs" version="04.04.00"><faqs><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Does ITW Insulated supply the chute installation kits?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;We have Nylon drive rivets and Twist fasteners available but are not included with the chute price.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Is it true that the Coated Nylon chutes have a problem with material shrinkage under extreme cold temperatures?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Yes the coated nylon material has been proven to shrink under extreme temperatures. ITW Insulated prepared installation instructions to allow for the shrinkage.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Is the Polyethylene chute lighter weight than the other chute material?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The 43 ft. Polyethylene chute weighs approximately 8 lbs versus the vinyl              at 21 lbs.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;What is the difference between the coated vinyl and the laminated vinyl?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The coated vinyl has no signs of delamination at the header area where    the continuous cold air causes the chute to flutter. The laminated vinyl has delamination issues. ITW Insulated chose to discontinue selling the laminated vinyl as of January 2009&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;What choice of material is available in the single temp air chutes?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The material available is the Polyethylene (PE), Coated Vinyl, Coated  	Nylon and Mesh.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;How are the chutes shipped?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The chutes are individually packaged and labeled. Up to 24 chutes can ship via UPS and 25 plus quantities will ship via LTL (Less than a truck load)&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Are all the chute headers different that attach to the Refrigeration unit?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;We need to know what type of reefer unit you have to ensure that the 	correct chute is ordered.  One exception; The UniMax Adapter and Chute set up. The UniMax Adapter and chute are considered “universal” and will accommodate all reefer units.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;What is the standard configuration?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Oblong grommets installed on the header and round grommets installed down the length of the chute.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;If I order a Velcro chute is that considered standard?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Velcro sewn to the chute is considered an option not standard.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;What sizes are considered stock chutes?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The stock chutes available are the 38 ft. and 43 ft. standard configuration.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;How many chute options are available to fit both Carrier and Thermo King units?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;ITW Insulated has many chute varieties to choose,  from stock to custom made.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq><faq><question><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;What is the purpose of a Single temperature refrigeration chute?&lt;/p&gt;]]></question><answer><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The air chute improves air flow by distributing from the refrigeration unit throughout the length of the trailer. This prevents the cold air from stopping directly in front of the refrigeration unit and being blocked by the product.&lt;/p&gt;]]></answer><catname><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catname><catdescription><![CDATA[Chute and Adapter]]></catdescription></faq></faqs></content>
